[
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (3x + 10) + (10x + 3)?",
      "correctAnswer": "13x + 13",
      "options": [
        "13x + 14",
        "14x + 13",
        "13x + 13",
        "12x + 13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (9x + 1) + (1x + 9)?",
      "correctAnswer": "10x + 10",
      "options": [
        "9x + 10",
        "11x + 10",
        "10x + 11",
        "10x + 10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (6x + 3) + (3x + 6)?",
      "correctAnswer": "9x + 9",
      "options": [
        "10x + 9",
        "9x + 10",
        "9x + 9",
        "8x + 9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (3x + 7) + (7x + 3)?",
      "correctAnswer": "10x + 10",
      "options": [
        "10x + 10",
        "9x + 10",
        "11x + 10",
        "10x + 11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (8x + 9) + (9x + 8)?",
      "correctAnswer": "17x + 17",
      "options": [
        "17x + 17",
        "18x + 17",
        "17x + 18",
        "16x + 17"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (5x + 1) + (1x + 5)?",
      "correctAnswer": "6x + 6",
      "options": [
        "6x + 7",
        "5x + 6",
        "6x + 6",
        "7x + 6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (6x + 3) + (3x + 6)?",
      "correctAnswer": "9x + 9",
      "options": [
        "9x + 9",
        "10x + 9",
        "8x + 9",
        "9x + 10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (10x + 6) + (6x + 10)?",
      "correctAnswer": "16x + 16",
      "options": [
        "16x + 16",
        "17x + 16",
        "16x + 17",
        "15x + 16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (2x + 3) + (3x + 2)?",
      "correctAnswer": "5x + 5",
      "options": [
        "5x + 5",
        "5x + 6",
        "6x + 5",
        "4x + 5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (9x + 6) + (6x + 9)?",
      "correctAnswer": "15x + 15",
      "options": [
        "14x + 15",
        "16x + 15",
        "15x + 16",
        "15x + 15"
      ]
    }
]